

CLARKY LEE

• DETAILS •

Mississauga, Canada +1 (647)-823-8395 howling.ape@gmail.com

o SKILLS o

Android Development

iOS Development

Unity

ReactiveX

GitHub

Java

Kotlin

Objective-C

Swift

C#

JavaScript

Ruby

• HOBBIES •

Karate, Sumo, Longboarding, Gaming, Music Production

PROFILE

Software engineering manager always looking for self-improvement, with 2+ years of engineer management experience and 9+ years of software development experience. Dedicated to leveling up engineers and guiding a project to success with my experience in full development life-cycles across several mobile games, and collaborating with other disciplines.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Engineering Manager at Zynga, Toronto

January 2019 — Present

Hands-on management with 5 software engineers over 2 mobile game teams:

- · Recruiting and leveling up the team; providing paths for career growth
- · Hands-on in full development life-cycle
- Tech scoping and planning
- · Identifying issues in and improving: team process, game pipelines and tech stack
- · Collaborating efforts across other teams and disciplines

Senior Software Engineer at Zynga, Toronto

July 2013 — December 2018

Working in agile-like processes to ship game client updates for several mobile game projects

- Full development life-cycle: design, implementation, testing, release & support
- · Coordinating feature experimentation and player analytics
- · Reacting to game metrics and app health analysis
- Working with product management to realize their vision
- Recruiting and mentoring interns

Software Engineer at Zynga, Toronto

July 2011 — June 2013

Working under senior staff direction across a few mobile game projects

- Feature implementation
- Feature iterations
- Bug fixes and patches

EDUCATION

Computer Science with Software Engineering Option, University of Waterloo, Waterloo September 2006 — April 2011

■ REFERENCES

• References available upon request